[
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Ampere"],
    "questionText": "What is the basic unit of electricity?",
    "options": ["Volt", "Ampere", "Watt", "Ohm"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Ammeter"],
    "questionText": "Which instrument is used to measure electric current?",
    "options": ["Voltmeter", "Ammeter", "Wattmeter", "Ohmmeter"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": [
      "DC flows in one direction, while AC changes direction periodically"
    ],
    "questionText": "What is the difference between Direct Current (DC) and Alternating Current (AC)?",
    "options": [
      "DC flows in one direction, while AC changes direction periodically",
      "AC flows in one direction, while DC changes direction periodically",
      "DC can travel long distances, while AC cannot",
      "AC can travel long distances, while DC cannot"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To protect the circuit from over current"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a fuse in an electrical circuit?",
    "options": [
      "To increase voltage",
      "To control current",
      "To protect the circuit from over current",
      "To protect the circuit from over voltage"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Wire Strippers"],
    "questionText": "Which tool is used to cut wires?",
    "options": ["Screwdriver", "Hammer", "Wire stripper", "Pliers"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Following safety rules"],
    "questionText": "What is the most important thing while working with electricity?",
    "options": [
      "Working quickly",
      "Using the right tools",
      "Following safety rules",
      "Using new tools"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "Which device is used to protect against electric shock?",
    "options": [
      "Fuse",
      "Circuit breaker",
      "Earthing/Grounding",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Three"],
    "questionText": "How many wires are typically used in household wiring?",
    "options": ["Two", "Three", "Four", "Five"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Gray or White"],
    "questionText": "What is the color of neutral wire?",
    "options": ["Black", "Red", "Green", "Gray or White"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Green or Green and Yellow"],
    "questionText": "What is the color of the earth wire?",
    "options": ["Black", "Red", "Green or Green and Yellow", "White"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["14 AWG"],
    "questionText": "Which wire guage is commonly used in household wiring?",
    "options": ["10 AWG", "14 AWG", "18 AWG", "22 AWG"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To protect the circuit from overcurrent"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a circuit breaker?",
    "options": [
      "To increase current",
      "To increase voltage",
      "To protect the circuit from overcurrent",
      "To protect the circuit from overvoltage"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Argon"],
    "questionText": "Which gas is filled in a ligh bulb?",
    "options": ["Oxygen", "Carbon dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Argon"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To increase or decrease voltage"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a transformer?",
    "options": [
      " To increase or decrease voltage",
      " To increase or decrease current",
      "To generate electricity",
      "To store electricity"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["50 Hertz"],
    "questionText": "What is the frequency of electricity used in households?",
    "options": ["25 Hertz", "50 Hertz", "60 Hertz", "100 Hertz"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Same in each component"],
    "questionText": "How does current flows in a series circuit?",
    "options": [
      "Different in each component",
      "Same in each component",
      "Flows through only one path",
      "Flows through two or more paths"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Same in each component"],
    "questionText": "How is the voltage drop in a parallel circuit?",
    "options": [
      "Different in each component",
      "Same in each component",
      "Flows through only one path",
      "Flows through two or more paths"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Miniature Circuit Breaker"],
    "questionText": "What does MCB stands for?",
    "options": [
      "Main Circuit Board",
      "Miniature Circuit Breaker",
      " Maximum Current Breaker",
      "Metal Circuit Board"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To measure electricity consumption"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of an electricity meter in a house?",
    "options": [
      "To generate electricity",
      "To measure electricity consumption",
      "To store electricity",
      "To Control Voltage"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["30 Amp circuit"],
    "questionText": "Which circuits are lights and fans usually connectd to in a house?",
    "options": [
      "15 Amp circuit",
      "20 Amp circuit",
      "30 Amp circuit",
      "50 Amp circuit"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Three"],
    "questionText": "How many voltages are there in a a three-phase supply?",
    "options": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "What factors should be considered while wiring a house?",
    "options": [
      "Correct wire size",
      "Proper use of circuit breakers",
      "Earthing/Grounding",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Main switch"],
    "questionText": "If the lights in the house are not working, what should be checked first?",
    "options": [
      "MCB at the meter board",
      "Light bulb",
      "Wiring",
      "Main switch"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Main switch"],
    "questionText": "If an appliance is not receiving current, what could be the reason?",
    "options": [
      "Fuse is blown",
      "MCB has tripped",
      "There is a fault in the wiring",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To check voltage"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a test light?",
    "options": [
      "To check voltage",
      "To check current",
      "To check resistance",
      "To check power"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Pakistan Electrical Code (PEC)"],
    "questionText": "Which electrical codes are applicable in Pakistan?",
    "options": [
      " National Electric Code (NEC)",
      "Pakistan Electrical Code (PEC)",
      "International Electrotechnical Commission (IEC)",
      "To check power"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Water and dust protection"],
    "questionText": "What does IP Code on electrical appliances indicate?",
    "options": [
      "Energy Efficiency",
      "Power Rating",
      "Water and dust protection",
      "Voltage rating"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Appliance needs to be earthed"],
    "questionText": "What does the earthing symbol on electrical appliances indicate?",
    "options": [
      "Appliance is double insulated",
      "Appliance needs to be earthed",
      " Appliance is waterproof",
      " Appliance is fireproof"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Air Conditioner"],
    "questionText": "Which appliance consumes the most electricity in a house?",
    "options": [
      " Refrigerator",
      "Air Conditioner",
      " Television",
      "Washing Machine"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Power consumption of the bulb"],
    "questionText": "The rating of a light bulb is in watts. What does this indicates?",
    "options": [
      "Brightness of the bulb",
      " Power consumption of the bulb",
      "Voltage of the bulb",
      "Lifespan of the bulb"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Mechanical energy"],
    "questionText": "Which energy is convertedinto electrical energy in an electric motor?",
    "options": [
      "Mechanical energy",
      "Thermal energy",
      "Light energy",
      "Chemcial energy"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "Why is regular maintenance of electrical appliances necessary?",
    "options": [
      "To improve perfomance",
      "To increase lifespan",
      "To ensure saftey",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "When should the brushes of an electric motor be inspected?",
    "options": [
      "When the motor is overheating",
      "When the motor is noisy",
      "When the motor stops working",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Yearly"],
    "questionText": "How often should MCBs be checked?",
    "options": ["Daily", "Weekly", "Monthly", "Yearly"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Ohm's Law"],
    "questionText": "What is the relationship between voltage, current and resistance?",
    "options": [
      "Ohm's Law",
      "Kirchoff's Law",
      " Faraday's Law",
      "Coulomb's Law"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["0.5 Kilowatt-hour"],
    "questionText": "How much energy will be consumed by burning a 100-watt bulbfor 5 hours?",
    "options": [
      "0.5 Kilowatt-hour ",
      "1 Kilowatt-hour",
      "5 Kilowatt-hour",
      "10 Kilowatt-hour"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["20 Ohms"],
    "questionText": "Two resistors of 10 ohms each are connected in series in a circuit. What will be their total resistance?",
    "options": ["5 Ohms ", "10 Ohms", "15 Ohms", "20 Ohms"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["10 Ohms"],
    "questionText": "  Two resistors of 20 ohms each are connected in parallel in a circuit. What will be their total resistance?",
    "options": ["10 Ohms ", "20 Ohms", "30 Ohms", "40 Ohms"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To convert electrical energy into mechanical energy"],
    "questionText": " What is the function of a DC motor?",
    "options": [
      " To generate electricity",
      "To convert electrical energy into mechanical energy",
      "To increase voltage",
      "To decrease current"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": " What is the difference between an AC motor and a DC motor?",
    "options": [
      "AC motor runs on AC supply, while DC motor runs on DC supply",
      "AC motor is more powerful than DC motor",
      "AC motor has higher speed then DC motor",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To convert mechanical energy into electrical energy"],
    "questionText": " What is the function of a generator?",
    "options": [
      "To convert mechanical energy into electrical energy",
      "To convert electrical energy into  mechanical energy",
      "To increase voltage",
      "To decrease current"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": " What happens if the bearings of the mtotr fails?",
    "options": [
      "Motor stops working",
      "Motor becomes noisy",
      "Motor overheats",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "If fuses are blowing repeatedly in a house, what could be the possible reasons?",
    "options": [
      "Overload",
      " Short circuit",
      " Old or faulty wiring",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Overload Relay"],
    "questionText": "Which device is used to protect a motor from overload?",
    "options": ["Fuse", "MCB", " Overload Relay", "ELCB"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "What is the difference between an LED bulb and a regular bulb?",
    "options": [
      "LED bulb saves more energy",
      "LED bulb has a longer lifespan",
      "LED bulbs produces less heat",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Solar energy"],
    "questionText": " Which energy does a solar panel convert into electrical energy",
    "options": [
      "Solar energy",
      "Wind energy",
      "Thermal energy",
      "Water energy"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To convert DC to AC"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of an inverter",
    "options": [
      "To convert DC to AC",
      "to convert DC to AC",
      "To increase voltage",
      "To decrease current"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": [" Kilowatt-hour"],
    "questionText": "What is the unit of measurement for electricity bills",
    "options": ["Volt", "Ampere", "Watt", " Kilowatt-hour"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Wire"],
    "questionText": "What does a straight line represent in an electrical diagram?",
    "options": ["Wire", "Switch", "Battery", "Bulb"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Lamp"],
    "questionText": "What does a circle with a cross inside represent in an electrical diagram?",
    "options": ["Lamp", "Resistor", "Capacitor", "Fuse"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Switch"],
    "questionText": "What does a rectangle with a line inside represent in an electrical diagram?",
    "options": ["Switch", "Battery", "Transformer", "Motor"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["AC Current"],
    "questionText": "What do wavy lines represents in an electrical diagram?",
    "options": [
      "Earthing/Grounding",
      "AC Current",
      "DC Current",
      "Neutral Wire"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Capacitor"],
    "questionText": "What does a symbol with two wires and a third line above them represents in an electrical diagram?",
    "options": ["Capacitor", "Transistor", "Diode", "Inductor"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Designing the circuit"],
    "questionText": "What is the first step in wiring a new house?",
    "options": [
      "Cutting wires",
      "Installing switch boards",
      "Installing lights",
      "Designing the circuit"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a conduit?",
    "options": [
      "To support wires",
      "To protect wires from weather",
      "To protect wires from rodents",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "Why are cable trays used?",
    "options": [
      "To organize cables",
      "To facilitate cable installation",
      "To make cable maintinance easier",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Three phase AC motor"],
    "questionText": "Which type of motor is a Star Delta Starter used for?",
    "options": [
      "DC motor",
      "Single phase AC motor",
      "Three phase AC motor",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Concealed wiring"],
    "questionText": "Which type of wiring is the safest for electrical appliances in a house?",
    "options": [
      "Open wiring",
      "Concealed wiring",
      "Cleat wiring",
      "Any wiring"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  }
]
